Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 47, Folder: 24 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Item 124: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. May 11, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 125: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. May 12, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 126: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. May 14, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 127: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. May 21, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 128: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. June 21, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 129: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. August 3, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 130: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. August 25, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 131: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. September 16, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 132: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. September 17, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 133: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. September 29, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 134: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. October 1, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 135: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. November 24, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 136: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. January 10, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 137: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. January 31, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 138: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. March 18, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 139: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. April 4, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 140: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. May 3, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 141: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. July 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 142: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. September 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 143: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. October 27, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 144: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. December 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 145: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. December 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 146: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. December 28, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 147: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. January 4, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 148: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. January 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 149: Employe Surveys Help Us, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. Reprinted from Synchroscope, December 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 150: Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. Revised September 11957. Item is in English.
  - Item 151: Findings of the Employe Survey, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By James W. Parker. Reprinted from Synchroscope, December 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 152: Where We Work: Orientation Unit of the Marysville Power Plant Job Training Program, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 153: Watch Your Step This Holiday Season, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Box: 47, Folder: 25 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Your New Job: A Handbook for New Employes, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. June 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Questionnaire For Use By Conference Leader: Principles of a Proposed Transfer and Promotion Policy for Non-Union Represented Jobs, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. November 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Supervisor Conference Unit: Principles of a Proposed Transfer and Promotion Policy, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: General Order no. 187: Employe Complaint Procedure, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. April 15, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Supervisor Conference Unit: Principles of a Proposed Transfer and Promotion Policy, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: General Order no.68: Pay During Absences, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. April 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: General Order no.68: Pay During Absences, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. April 3, 1947. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: General Order no.73: Private Work by Employes, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. April 25, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: General Order no.136: Vacations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. December 28, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: General Order no.136: Vacations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. December 28, 1953. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: General Order no.142: Medical Policy and Procedures, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. August 25, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: General Order no.155: Purchaces by Employes, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. November 25, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: General Order no.155: Purchaces by Employes, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. November 25, 1947. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: General Order no.164: Employment Policy and Procedures, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. August 28, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: General Order no.175: Military Service, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 16: General Order no.180: Employe Relations Departments, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. September 23, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: General Order no.186: Pay Practices, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. March 23, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: General Order no.186: Pay Practices, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. March 23, 1949. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: General Order no.190: Salary Policy and Practices, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. November 15, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: General Order no.191: Disciplinary Procedure, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. March 17, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: General Order no.194: Safety Policy and Procedures, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. March 25, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: General Order no.201: Layoff Policy, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. October 25, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: General Order no.202: Pay During Extended Disability, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. November 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: General Order no.203: Promotions and Transfers, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. May 10, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: General Order no.207: Employe Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. March 15, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: General Order no.212: Induction of New Employes, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. December 18, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Routine Instructions no.100: Patents and Inventions, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. April 24, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Technician Opportunites at Detroit Edison, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 29: Handbook For Edison People, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. September, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Your Opportunity is with Detroit Edison: An Equal Opportunity Employer, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 31: General Order no.177: Table of Organization, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. January 1,1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: General Order no.177: Corporate Organization Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. January 1, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Guide to Management Development, August 1970, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. August, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Synchroscope: Minority Progress Through Affirmative Action, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. October, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Detroit EdisonToday, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. v.7:no.25 (1979:Dec. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Management Report, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. v.4:no.25 (1979:Dec. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Some Rules of Conduct for Employees, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 38: Professional Manpower Performance Review, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Box: 47, Folder: 26 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Supervisors Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Box: 47, Folder: 27 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Supervisors Handbook Material, Publication (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Supervisors Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Box: 47, Folder: 28 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. December, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
    By The Detroit Edison Company. July, 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 47, Folder: 29 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Hourly Pay Practices, Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
    By Detroit Labor Trends. Item is in English.
- Box: 47, Folder: 30 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Manual of Safe Practice, Use, and Handling of Factory Chemicals, Publication (Box 47, Folder 30)
    By Detroit Plant Chemical Control. Item is in English.
- Box: 47, Folder: 31 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing Trusts, Publication (Box 47, Folder 31)
    By Vance L. Desmond. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Assessment Centers Help with People Decisions, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    By Development Dimensions Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Attend a National Conference on Interaction Management, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The Assessment Center Method, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Proof! A supervisory Training System that Really Works., Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Assessment Center Method, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Assessment Center Method, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Attend a National Conference on Interaction Management, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Development Dimensions, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Box: 48, Folder: 2 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Salt: The Story of Diamond Crystal Salt, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    By Diamond Crystal Salt Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 3 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Five Worlds of Diamond Shamrock Chemicals, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
    By Diamond Shamrock Corp. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: World; Great music comes alive for millions of people the world over, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Box: 48, Folder: 4 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employees' Handbook; for the plant of R. E. Dietz Co., Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
    By R.E. Dietz Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Contributory Life, Accidental Death and Dismemberment and Accident and Sickness Insurance, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
    By Robert Dietz. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 5 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: This Is DISCUS: Information; Leadership; Research; Service, Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
    By Distilled Spirits Council of the US. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: DISCUS Fact Book 1979: The Beverage Alcohol Industry; Public Attitudes and Economic Patterns, Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Alcoholism Programs in Business, Industry, Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Box: 48, Folder: 6 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Standard Plan for Employees' Profit- Sharing and Retirement Trusts, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
    By The Distributors Group, Inc. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 7 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Apprenticeship News, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
    By Division of Apprenticeship Standards. v.40:no.4 (1981:Oct.). Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 8 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Eye to Eye: An Adventure in Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 48, Folder 8)
    By Doehler-Jarvis Corp. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 9 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Plan; Factors, Description of Factors, Degree and Point Values, Publication (Box 48, Folder 9)
    By Dominion Textile Company Limited. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: OTIS- Quick Scoring Mental Ability Tests; Gamma Test: Form C., Publication (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Examins Otis-Ottawa D'Habilete Mentale, Publication (Box 48, Folder 9)
    By Dominion Textile Company Limited. Item is in French.
  - Item 4: Dominion Textile: Employer, Producer, Taxpayer, Publication (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Textile Age; The Story of Dominion Textile Co., Inc., Publication (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Box: 48, Folder: 10 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 48, Folder 10)
    By Dominick & Dominick. November 18, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Railroad Industry Survey, Publication (Box 48, Folder 10)
    By Dominick & Dominick. March 4, 1965. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 11 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Lakeside Press: Training Craftsmen, Publication (Box 48, Folder 11)
    By R.R. Donnelley & Sons Co. v.4:no.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The School For Apprentices of The Lakeside Press, Publication (Box 48, Folder 11)
    By R.R. Donnelley & Sons Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Study Of The School For Apprentices Of The Lakeside Press, Publication (Box 48, Folder 11)
    By Carl Dewitt Davis. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Some Responsibilities of General Management, Publication (Box 48, Folder 11)
    By C. C. Haffner, Jr. Address given at the 29th Annual Meeting of the Graphic Arts Association of Illinois. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 12 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Special Accident Insurance: Salaried Employes, Publication (Box 48, Folder 12)
    By Douglas Aircraft Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Salaried Employes' Pension Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 12)
    By Douglas Aircraft Co. December 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Douglas Salaried Employes Savings Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 12)
    By Douglas Aircraft Co. July 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Hourly Employees Pension Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 12)
    By Douglas Aircraft Co. December 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Pension Plan For Salaried Employes, Publication (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Fire and Safety regulations, Publication (Box 48, Folder 12)
    By Douglas Aircraft Co. January 24, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Your merit Review: An outline of Employe Analysis rating, Publication (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Box: 48, Folder: 13 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Your Medical Care Program, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.1: Medical Care. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Long Term Disability Income Protection Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.2: Income Replacement. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.3: Retirement Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Your Dow retirement Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Group Insurance For Dow Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.4: Life and Accident Insurance. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Business Travel Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Your Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Your Stock Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.8: Savings and Investments. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Your Dental Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.10: Other Programs. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.10: Other Programs. Blank personnel form. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Dental Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Your Home is Full of Surprises: A guide to home safety, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.11: Safety Programs. Includes envelope for mailing this pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Your Estate Inventory, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
    By Dow Chemical Company. In File no.12: General. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Your Dow benefits, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Where there's A Will, There's a Way, Publication (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Box: 48, Folder: 14 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Learn to Do Something, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
    By Dow Chemical Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Elements, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Some facts about Dow in Midland, Michigan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Salaried Empoyees handbook, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Getting or Changing a Job Demands Planning, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
    By G. Robert Baker. Reprinted from Chemical and Engineering News, v.42 (1964:Jan. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Improving Research and Development Relations Bewteen Universities and Industry, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
    By C. A. Gerstacker. Remarks for Panel Discussion at the World Congress on Engineering Education, June 28, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Grow With Dow International, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: The Dow Story, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: The Creativity Review, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
    By Dow Chemical Company. v.8:no.1 (1966:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Letter to Gordon Law, Publication (Box 48, Folder 14)
    By Wayne M. Hancock. December 17, 1974. Item is in English.
- Box: 48, Folder: 15 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Though Starters Regarding "Pot of Gold", Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Willard H. Dow. Thought Starter Series no.109. Address given at Columbia University, May 20, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Professionalism in Industry: The Dow Story, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By H. P. Cooper. Reprinted from American Engineer, December, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Job Security and productivity improvement, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Personnel Forms, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. Envelope containing 14 blank pesonnel forms. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Plant Rules for Employees of The Midland Division, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Grace A. Dow Memorial Library, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Midland and its Schools, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Midland Public Schools: Adult Education Program, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. School Year: 1960-1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The City of Midland Michigan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Personal Summary, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. Blank personnel form. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Housing Available in Midland, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: College Interview Summary, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Technical Service Opportunities at Dow, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Technical Employment Personal Data Sheet, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Employment Application, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: College Scholarship Letter, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: The Dow Chemical Company Information Sheet, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: The Dow Chemical Company Information Sheet, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. Copy 2. Includes 2 blank personnel forms. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Policy of the Dow Chemical Company Concerning the Transportation and Moving Expenses of New Employees reporting to Work, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: Opportunities with The Dow Chemical Company, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 21: Now! Pay all your bills with one convenient payroll deduction plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: Plus values for You, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 23: The Aid-to-Education Program of The Dow Chemical Company, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By David H. Morgan. Address given at the 39th Annual Meeting of the National Industrial Conference Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Your Credit Union: a guide to prosperity, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 25: The Facts on SRP, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 26: Your Credit uniot Protects your finacial Security, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 27: Plus Values For You, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 28: The Dow Chemical Employees' Credit union Story, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 29: Group Insurance for Dow Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 30: The Dow Matching Grant Plan: An Employee Aid-for-Education Program, 1957-1960, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 31: Supplementary Retirement Plan and Trsut Agreement, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 32: The Dow Chemical Company Stock Shares, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. Prospectus. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Pension and Profit Sharing Plan and Trust Agreement, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 34: You Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Item 35: Dow Diamond, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. v.27:no.2 (1964:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Brinewell, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. v.18:no.6 (1959:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Dow Diamond, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)
    By Dow Chemical Company. v.27:no.3 (1964). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Et Cetera, Publication (Box 48, Folder 15)